wgiftcard.com 2016-06-11

# » Transaction Wireless >

This privacy statement (“Privacy Policy”) covers the websites and social media pages owned and operated by Transaction Wireless, Inc. (“Transaction Wireless”, “we”, “us”, “our”) and use of and access to our Gateway Servers (the “Servers”) and all other products and services provided by Transaction Wireless (collectively, the “Service”). We know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our websites, submitting information, or otherwise accessing or using the Service, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. Transaction Wireless abides by the [Safe Harbor Privacy Principles Framework](http://export.gov/safeharbor/eu/eg_main_018475.asp) and [Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act](http://laws-lois.justice.gc.ca/eng/acts/p-8.6/). 

**1\. Scope.**  
This Privacy Policy covers Transaction Wireless’ treatment of personal information that Transaction Wireless gathers when you are on any of our websites or otherwise use or access the Service. Also, this Privacy Policy covers Transaction Wireless’ treatment of any personal information that Transaction Wireless’ business partners share with Transaction Wireless. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Transaction Wireless does not own or control, or to individuals that Transaction Wireless does not employ or manage.

**2\. Information Collected.**  
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to personalize and improve the Service. We collect the following types of information from our users: email address, phone number, number of gift cards purchased or owned, number and date of visits, the device used to access and other Information you provide to us when using the Service.  
We may receive and store any information you enter on our websites or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. Any credit card information collected such as account number, CVV and expiration date is NOT stored by Transaction Wireless and is only used only for the purpose of completing a sale. Please see section 4 for more information. 

**3\. Information We Automatically Collect.**  
We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Service. Generally, the Service may automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our websites. This data is only used in the aggregate, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of collective data enables us to figure out how often users use parts of the Service, so we can make the Service appealing to as many users as possible. In addition, we may provide statistical information (not information about you personally) to our partners about how our users, collectively, use the Service.

**4\. Information Collected by the Servers.**  
If you use our products to access the Servers, certain information processed by the Servers (such as, credit card numbers, credit card security numbers, etc.) will not be stored. Other information (such as, date/time stamp, authorization number, etc.) will be collected and stored, but only for statistical analysis purposes in order for us to improve the quality of the Service. Transaction Wireless treats all credit card data securely under the [PCI DSS standards](http://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/). Any information collected by the Servers will not be shared with other third parties or used for any other reason. IF YOU CHOOSE TO ACCESS THE SERVERS BY OTHER MEANS (I.E. WITHOUT USING OUR PRODUCTS), THEN THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS NOT APPLICABLE TO YOU.

**5\. Uses of Personal Information Collected.**  
The personal information you provide may be used for such purposes as sending you information about our company or our features, products or services, or promotional materials from some of our partners, or to contact you when we deem it necessary. We also may use your personal information for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users’ behavior, for product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements, and to customize content and layout of our websites. Names, postal and e-mail addresses and phone numbers collected may be added to our databases and used for mailings regarding website updates, new products and services, upcoming events and the status of orders placed online where not prohibited by applicable law. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please notify us support@wgiftcard.com.

**6\. Use of Social Media.**  
Transaction Wireless and its agents may collect information from various social media sources: Facebook, Twitter, etc. (“Social Media”) which may be used in marketing and sales materials.

**7\. Sharing of Information.**  
We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only with your consent or to the business partners and affiliates as described below:  
Affiliates we do not control. At certain times, we may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling subscriptions, orders, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service. These other companies and individuals have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. You hereby consent to our sharing of your personal information for the above purposes.  
Personnel. Our personnel (including, for the avoidance of doubt, consultants and/or contractors) may have access to personal information while carrying out their duties in the normal course of our company business.

**8\. Business Transfers.**  
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy websites, companies or assets. In such transactions, traffic data and personal information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that Transaction Wireless, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, personal information will, of course, be one of the transferred assets.  
Protection of Transaction Wireless or Others. We will, without specific or further notice to you, release your personal information when we believe such disclosure is appropriate to: (a) comply with law or a court order or other legal process (b) protect the rights, property or safety of Transaction Wireless, the Service, our users or others or (c) enforce our Terms of Use.

**9\. Information Security.**  
Your information is protected by SSL encryption and such other methods as we have determined are appropriate given the nature of our business. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. Transaction Wireless is a U.S. entity. Accordingly, your information collected and used by Transaction Wireless is generally stored in the U.S. and is therefore accessible to law enforcement, governmental and regulatory authorities according to applicable U.S. laws. 

**10\. Access to Information.**  
In some cases you may be able to access your personal information on our websites and correct or amend information that is inaccurate. If you wish to do so, please contact us at support@wgiftcard.com.

**11\. Links to Other Websites.**  
Our websites may from time to time contain links to other websites. These other websites are not under our control. We are not responsible for the privacy and security practices of such websites.

**12\. Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy.**  
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice (except where required by law), to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, by posting such change, update or modification on any of our websites. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon such posting.

**13\. Conditions of Use Revisions.**  
If you choose to visit our websites, or otherwise use or access our Service, your visit and all disputes over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the state of California. If you have any concern about privacy at our websites or otherwise with respect to the Service, please send us a thorough description of your concerns to support@wgiftcard.com, and we will make every effort to resolve the issue. Our business changes constantly. This Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use will also change, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use, where not prohibited by applicable law. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our websites frequently to familiarize yourself with any changes to this Privacy Policy.

**14\. Effective Date of This Privacy Policy.**  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of September 24, 2015.
